前情提要...
Previously on Lost...
你可以回去了
You can go back to your camp.
那我的朋友呢?
What about my friends?
你要做的是回去告诉你们的人
Your job is to tell the rest of your people
永远不要来找我们
they can never come here.
安息吧 Eko先生
Rest in peace, Mr.Eko.
谢谢你帮我找到...
And thank you for helping me find my...
抬起你的头向北看 John
我不在乎Jack怎么说
I don't care what Jack said.
我们要把他找回来
They've got him, and we have to get him back.
这是我欠他的
I owe him that.
珍珠站是一个监控站
The pearl is a monitoring station
此舱用于监视和观察
where the activities of participants in the Dharma initiative projects
达摩实验的参与者
can be observed and recorded.
他一定在等待我们
I guess he'll be expecting us.
乒乓台?
Ping-Pong table?
这东西从哪儿弄来的?
Where the hell did that come from?
Jin在我们找木柴的时候找到的
Jin found it when he was out looking for firewood.
我们做了桌子腿和球拍
We made legs for it and paddles.
我们需要的是球
Now all we need is a ball.
是找到的?
Found it?
一定是舱里爆炸后飞出来的
Must have landed in the jungle when the hatch exploded.
我以为舱里只是倒塌了
I thought the hatch collapsed.
我只知道天空变成了紫色
Look, dude, all I know is the sky turned purple.
从那以后 我就不再问问题了 我要开始新的生活
After that, I don't ask questions, just make myself a salad and move on.
是啊 那还真管用
Yeah, I can see that's working for you.
你看见kate了吗?
You seen Kate around?
她还没回来吗?
she's not back yet?
有什么东西能当球打吗?
You guys find anything we can use for a ball?
没有
No
那是我的"枪支与军火"
Hey, that's my "Guns & Ammo."
怎么会在你手里?
Where the hell did you get it?
我在杂志堆里找到的
It was in the magazine stack.
现在我们资源共享了
We share things now.
听着Zorro 这是我的东西...
Listen, Zorro, it was in my stuff...
当你们以为我死了的时候
Stuff you decided to have a little party with
你们就用我的东西开派对了?
while you thought I was dead.
听着 Hillbilly 如果你想要的话 就拿去吧
Listen, Hillbilly, if you want it that bad, take it.
自己留着吧
Just keep it.
我们得吃东西了
We need to eat.
我们的方向对吗?
Are we still on course?
我们依然朝着北方3-0-5方向前进
We're still heading north on a bearing of 3-0-5.
是的
Yes.
我感到你缺乏信心
I'm sensing a lack of confidence.
我们跟着那棍子上的雕刻
We've been walking for two days
已经走了两天了
following a compass bearing provided by the carvings on a stick.
那么?
And?
你真的认为 这会帮助我们找到"the others"的营地吗?
You really think we're just going to chance upon where the others are?
我不知道我们还会遇到什么
I don't know what we're gonna chance on
但这是我们唯一的方向
but my bearing is the only bearing we got.
我要去找些水果 然后
I'm going to find some fruit,and then,
John 我们要好好谈谈下一步的行动了
John, we're going to have a rational conversation regarding our next move.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：    许愿
校对： 许愿
■
双语字幕：    七色九天    HUXI
后期：     梁良      字幕监制：  梁良
■
你们在找...这个吧?
You'all looking for something like... this?
酷 一个球
Cool, a ball.
我们要来个小小的交易
We need to do a little quid pro quo first.
我离开这里有段时间了
I know I've been gone a while
你们就认为可以把我的东西
and you'all thought the general store
拿到百货商场廉价出售
was having a going out of business sale
但我回来了 我想要回我的东西
but now I'm back, and I want what's mine.
但那些东西原本也不是你的
Yeah, but it wasn't really yours to begin with.
"A"-- 那些是我找到的
"A"-- It was mine when I took it.
"B"-- 你又是谁?
"B"-- Who the hell are you?
"C"-- 我很公平 我们用比赛决定
And "C"-- Because I'm fair, I'm gonna let you play me for it.
打乒乓球?
Play ping-Pong?
是啊 大块头
That's right, Avalanche.
你们这群家伙尽管挑个打得最好的
You bastards put up your best player.
就一场比赛 我赢了之后
One game, and when I crush them
你们要把我的每样东西都还给我
you'all gotta bring me every piece of my stash back.
如果你输了呢?
And if you lose?
我不会输的 但...
I ain't gonna lose, but..
如果我输了...随你们怎么样
if I do, tell you what...name it.
看来"卧虎藏龙"有好的主意
Looks like Crouching Tiger and Hidden Dragon got something good.
说吧
Lay it on me.
不许再叫我们的绰号
No nicknames.
如果你输了 一个星期内...
If you lose, no nicknames for anyone...
不许叫我们的绰号
for a week.
好棒
Nice.
成交
You're on.
选出你们的选手吧
Pick your player.
一小时后我会回来 然后我会宰了你们
I'll be back in an hour, then let the slaughter begin.
你确定这房子周围什么都没有？
Are you sure it's completely isolated?
我搜索过周边地带
I've circled the house.
附近除了丛林什么都没有
There's nothing but jungle surrounding it.
给你
Here.
那个雷达还能工作吗?
That dish still work?
这样的卫星雷达
A satellite dish of that size would have
能传播几千英里的信息
broadcasting capabilities for thousands of miles.
Danielle 你提到过雷达站
Danielle, you once mentioned a radio tower.
是这个吗?
Is this it?
我从来没有来过这里
I have never been here before.
那里面的男人...你说你见过他?
The man in the house...you said you've seen him before?
就是珍珠站录像里的那个人
On a video feed from the pearl station.
那他是谁?
So who is he?
只有一种办法能找到答案...
Only one way to find out...
我们去问他
we ask him.
这是干嘛?
What's this for?
如果我不带武器 他就不会感到有威胁
If I'm unarmed, he won't feel threatened.
如果他有所动作 你从这里掩护我
In case he is threatened, you can cover me from here.
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
我对那房子里的男人没兴趣
I have no interest in that man inside the house.
我能生存下来是因为我尽量避免与他们正面接触
I have survived on the island precisely by avoiding these types of encounters.
我会在小溪边等你们...
I'll wait for you by the stream...
等能活下来的
for those of you who survive.
Najeev Najeev
有个人想要见你
这是你做的吗?
Did you cook this?
是的
Yes, I did.
这很美味
It's delicious.
我叫Sami
My name is Sami.
Najeev 谢谢你
Najeev. Thank you.
请坐
Please sit.
你从哪里来 Najeev?
So where are you from, Najeev?
我是Syrian人
I'm Syrian.
拜托
Please.
你和我一样是伊拉克人吧 年轻人
你想怎么样?
What do you want from me?
你是个出色的厨师 我...
You're an excellent cook, and I...
有一个很好的餐馆
I have a restaurant much nicer than this place.
来看看吧
Come take a look.
如果你喜欢 我会付你双倍的工资
If you like it, I will hire you at twice your pay here.
就凭一顿饭你就会雇佣一个陌生人?
You're offering a stranger a job because of a single meal?
我给你工作是因为我和你都是外来者
I'm offering you a job because we are outsiders here
我的主厨刚好辞职了
and because, uh, my chef just quit.
他中弹了
He's been hit, he's been hit!
你也想被射到吗?
You wanna get shot, too?
我没有越线!
I didn't cross the line!
我们有停战协议的
We had a truce.
这是我的地盘!
This is my land!
我不是...你们说我可以待在这里的!
I'm not.. You said I could stay here!
我不是..你说的那个人
I'm not who you..Who you think I am.
我叫Sayid Jarrah
My name is Sayid Jarrah.
几个月前我们的飞机坠毁了
I was on a plane that crashed here months ago.
飞机?!
A plane?!
我发誓我没有武器!
I'm unarmed, I swear!
待在那儿别动!
Stay right there!
把枪扔掉!
Drop the rifle!
快点扔掉
Drop it right now!
退后
Back up.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
你们的飞机真的坠毁了?
You really did crash here?
是的 我们还有40多个人
Over 40 of us, yes.
我先进去看看
I'll go in first, make sure it's okay.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我叫Mikhail Bakunin...
My name is Mikhail Bakunin...
我是达摩计划的最后一个存活成员
and I am the last living member of the Dharma Initiative.
小心脚下
Watch your step.
请坐
Please...Sit.
让我来
Here, let me.
你有治疗枪伤的经验?
You've had experience treating gunshot wounds?
我在阿富汗待了一段时间
I spent some time in Afghanistan.
获得了一些战地救助的经验...
I had experience with field medicine...
我在苏联的部队里
in the Soviet army.
厨房里架子上有医疗用品
In the kitchen on the top shelf there is a medical kit.
请你把它拿过来
Will you bring it, please?
没关系的 Kate
It's all right, Kate.
你怎么到这里来的?
How did you get here?
我不知道该从何说起
I almost don't know where to begin.
为什么你不和我说说达摩组织呢?
Why don't you begin with the Dharma Initiative?
我在kiev长大并加入了军队
I grew up in Kiev and joined the Soviet army.
我在vladivostok一个监听站服役
I was stationed at a listening post in Vladivostok.
冷战结束后
After the cold war...
我们冷战输了以后，我们的小队被解散了
After we lost the cold war, my unit was decommissioned.
我离开了军队
I was dismissed from my life in the military,
经过了那么多年和敌人的战斗
and after years of conducting unpleasant actions against our enemies
我发现我想做些好事
I found myself wanting to do something good
后来我被一则报纸上的广告所吸引
so I replied to a newspaper advertisement.
一则广告?
An advertisement?
"你想拯救世界吗?" 它写到
"Would you like toave the world?" It read.
我就是这样知道这个组织的
That's how I met the Initiative.
他们很有钱也很聪明 但必须对外保密
They're very secretive, very rich and very smart.
那么你是什么时候来的?
So when did you come to the island?
11年前
11 years now.
我喜欢电脑 通讯设备
I liked computers, communications equipment
喜欢像灯塔守夜人一样孤独的生活
and being alone like a lighthouse keeper
他们就让我到这个站来了
so they put me in this station.
他们称为"火焰舱"
They called it "The Flame."
火焰舱的用途是什么?
What's the purpose of The Flame?
当然是和外界通讯
To communicate with the outside world, of course.
准备好了吗?
Ready to play?
到你了
Your move.
达摩组织发生了什么事?
What happened to the Dharma Initiative?
他们全死了
They're all dead, of course.
他们愚蠢的发起了对"敌人"的战争
They foolishly initiated a war against the hostiles
他们叫作"大清洗"
a "purge," they called it.
那你是怎么幸存下来的?
And how did you survive this purge?
我没有参与其中
By not participating in it.
我告诉过你
I told you.
我喜欢独自行动
I like being alone.
那"敌人"们允许你住在这里?
And the hostiles allowed you to stay here?
当一切都结束后 4个人出现在我的田地里
After it was over, four men appeared in the yard.
并提出停战协定
They offered a truce.
他们在各个地方划出界限
They said to imagine a line that extended all the way around the valley.
如果我不越线 他们就不会管我
As long as I did not cross it, I would be left alone.
然后他们带走两头牛 我再也没看到过它们
Then they took two cows, and I never saw them again.
他们对那个卫星雷达不感兴趣?
They weren't interested in the satellite dish in the yard?
那又怎么样?
Why would they be?
那个东西几年前就没用了
It hasn't functioned for years.
他们是谁..这些"敌人"?
Who are they..these hostiles?
我不知道 但他们比我们先到这里
I do not know, but they were here for a long time before we were
早很多
A very long time.
我在找Sami
I'm looking for Sami.
Sami!
很高兴你能来
I'm so glad you came.
你觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
这是一个简洁的地方 我们有很好的客人
It's a simple place, as you can see, but we have good customers.
这是我的夫人
Here's my wife.
她主管厨房
She's in charge of the kitchen.
Amira 来见Najeev
Amira, come meet Najeev.
很高兴见到你
Pleasure to meet you.
你确定是他么?
Are you sure this is him?
是的
Yes.
你们一定搞错了...
Look, I don't know who you think I am...
你刚才说什么?
What did you just say?
我告诉Nadia礼貌点 因为你们是我的客人
I told Nadia to be polite, because you are my guests.
Nadia?
Nadia Comaneci最出色的体操运动员
After Nadia Comaneci, the greatest athlete the world has ever known.
我们的生日是同一天
We have the same birthday.
现在...
Now...
伤口弄好了
excellent work, if I say myself.
谢谢你 Mikhail
Thank you, Mikhail.
也许我可以为你们弄些冰茶
Perhaps...I can begin to earn your forgiveness by offering some iced tea.
我去看看你们的朋友
I will also check on your friend.
别浪费时间了
Don't waste your time.
十年来我一直想办法打败电脑
For ten years I've tried to defeat that game.
但这个程序是3个博士编写的...
But it was programmed by three grand masters...
而且它还作弊
and it cheats.
我玩过许多电脑
Well I've played a lot of computers
而且很肯定它们不懂怎么作弊
and I'm pretty sure they don't know how to cheat.
这就是为什么我们人类是这么...
That's what makes being human so distinctly...
奇妙
wonderful.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
这...根本没道理
It just...it doesn't make any sense.
他为什么让John和那么多设备器材待在一起?
Why would they let him stay here, with all this stuff, all this equipment?
这再合理不过了
Actually, it makes perfect sense.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
他让我们待在这儿 因为他不是达摩的人
The reason they let him stay here is because he is not Dharma.
他是"他们"的人
He is one of them.
他射了你 你还...
He shot you, and you just let him...
我们为什么还待在这儿?
Why are we still sitting here?
我们要待在这里 Kate
We are sitting here, Kate
我确信不止他一个人在这儿
because I am certain he is not alone.
你真的是最棒的吗 大怪脸?
So...you really the number one draft pick, Grimace?
我们用的是"宽容规则"吗?
Are we playing with the mercy rule?
宽容规则?
Mercy rule?
如果我打出11比0 那我就赢了
Yeah,like,If I'm up 11-0, then I, you know, automatically win.
你想赢我11比0?
You're gonna go up 11-0?
不 规则适用双方选手
No, I mean either one of us.
当然
Sure.
我们可以用这个规则
We can have a mercy rule.
我能发球吗?
Do you wanna volley for serve?
随便你
I'll tell you what...Be my guest.
干掉他 Hurley
Take him down, Hurley.
加油 Hurley
0比0
0 serving 0.
1比0
1-Nothing.
我自己做的茶 如果有点苦的话请别介意
I grow the tea myself, so pardon its bitterness.
我们十分感激
Any tea is good tea.
我们很长时间没见过冰了
You know how long it's been since we've seen ice?
我发现站周围有许多粗电线
I noticed a series of thick wires as I walked around the station.
这是网络集线器
This is the hub,
和这岛上的其它站相连接
but they go underground to various stations all over the island.
有没有一根是通向大海的?
And these cables--do any of them run into the ocean?
是的 海底电缆连接的声纳
Yes. There is an underwater beacon that emits sonar pings
为船只导航
to help guide in the vessels.
导航 你是说潜水艇吗?
By vessels, you mean submarines?
是的
Yes.
并且它有自主判断能力
The Initiative used one to bring us here
但现在它不是被"敌人"销毁
but I can imagine only that the hostiles have either destroyed
就是被他们操控了
or commandeered it by now.
这就能解释他们
That explains how they were able
饶开我的位点 并夺走了我们的帆船
to get round my position and capture our sailboat.
你们有帆船?
You have a sailboat?
直到被"敌人"抢走
Till we lost it to your hostiles.
那太不幸了
That's very unfortunate.
至少我们能杀了其中的一个人
Well...at least we were able to kill one them.
我们为什么还要兜圈子呢...
Why are we continuing to play this little game...
为什么不直接切入正题?
when we all know it has moved to the next stage?
拿些绳子来
Get some rope.
喝了它
Drink.
你在共和国卫队里是个拷问官吧?
You were a torturer, were you not, in the Republican Guard?
难道你认不出你的受害者了?
Do you not recognize one of your victims?
难道你不记得被你折磨的女人了吗?
Do you not recognize the woman that you tortured?
难道你认不出我妻子了吗?!
Do you not recognize my wife?!
不 我...
No, I've never...
你一定是搞错了
You've confused me with someone else.
Amira因为窝藏敌人的罪名被捕了
Amira was arrested for harboring an enemy of the state.
在她被关押的3个月间 她被拷问无数次
She was held for three months while she was questioned.
她的手臂上满是伤疤
Her arms bear the scars of those questions.
我向你保证 Najeev 我没有弄错
So I assure you, Najeev, I am not confused.
我的名字不是Najeev
My name is not Najeev.
我叫Sayid Jarrah
I am Sayid Jarrah.
我曾在共和国卫队
I was in the Republican Guard
而且我是个拷问官 但我从来没见过你的妻子
and, yes, I was an interrogator, but I have never seen your wife.
也许她在哪里见过我
Maybe she saw me at the same facility
但我的确不认识她!
but I do not know her!
我记得每一个我拷问的人
I can remember every face of every person I've interrogated.
她记得你的脸
She remembers your face.
她一踏进你们的饭店
She remembers it so well that she recognized it from a mere glimpse
就认出你来了!
when we walked by the restaurant where you worked!
你要我做什么?
What do you want from me?
我要你承认你所做的 否则
I want you to admit to what you did, And if you don't
你想要离开这里 只有被装进那包里了
you will leave this room in that bag.
你怎么知道他不是一个人?
How do you know he isn't alone?
外面的那匹马还装有马鞍
The horse outside is still saddled
而且马镫的设置比这个男人的脚要短许多
And the stirrups are set up for someone much shorter than this man.
你认为"The others"派人来让他合作?
You think the others sent someone to keep him company?
他们派人来是因为他们失去了联系
They sent someone out here because they lost communications.
也许是因为天空变成了紫色?
Maybe when the sky turned purple?
这正是我所想的
That would be my guess.
如果有人在这里的话 他一定藏的很好
If there's someone else here, they're hiding pretty good.
我检查过这地方的每个角落...
I checked every nook and cranny of this place...
还不够彻底
Not every nook and cranny.
你准备好说实话了吗?
Are you ready to tell me the truth?
我已经把实话告诉你了
I have told you the truth.
我不认识你
I do not know you
你折磨过她!
You tortured her.
不
No.
我从不碰女人
I would never touch a woman
你认为这样做
Do you think this will do any good
会让我承认我没做过的事?
that this will make me confess to something I didn't do?
我妻子说了实话
My wife confessed to something she didn't do.
而你却用烧开的油烫她的手臂
She confessed when you poured a pan of boiling oil over her arms.
不 你一定弄错了...
No, I did not. You have the wrong...
承认吧!
Admit it!
我不能承认我没做过的事
I cannot admit to something I didn't do.
今天到此为止吧
That is enough for today.
我明天还会再来
Then I will see you tomorrow.
到你了
Your move.
Your move
那是什么?
What is it?
C-4...
炸药
explosive.
布满了整个地方
The whole place is wired.
为什么?
Why ?
我不知道
I don't know.
到你了
Your move
你赢了!
You win!
手动命令启动
Manual override achieved.
放下集装盘 请输入2-4
For pallet drop, enter 2-4.
站台卫星上行链路 请输入3-2
For station uplink, enter 3-2.
连接大陆 请输入3-8
For mainland communication, enter 3-8.
卫星天线已损坏
The satellite dish is inoperable.
连接失败
Communications are down.
进入声纳 请输入5-6
For sonar access, enter 5-6.
声纳已损坏
Sonar is inoperable.
如果这个站点已被"敌人"入侵
Has there been an incursion on this station by the hostiles?
请输入7-7
If so, enter 7-7.
小声点 把你的手放在胸前
Keep your voice low and your hands in front of you.
住手
Stop right there.
把枪放下...快点
Put the gun on the ground... now.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
就是她
It's her.
她在那儿!
She was there!
那个码头
She was at the dock.
我们被绑架的时候她在场
She was there when we were kidnapped.
她知道Jack在哪里
She knows where Jack is.
还有其他人在这里吗?
Are there any more of you here?
把她弄到搂上去
Let's take her upstairs.
John 我们上来了!
Come on. John, we're coming up!
John!
在这边
Out here.
快走
Move.
很简单
This is simple.
把她交给我 我就放了他
Send her over to me, and I will release him.
然后我们各走各的路
Then we all go our separate ways.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
如果他要杀我 我早死了
If he was gonna kill me, I'd be dead already.
给我闭嘴
Shut your mouth.
-听我说  -Sayid别让她跑了
-Listen to me.  -Sayid, do not let her go.
我现在就能杀了你
I will execute you right here
-他不会的  -别说了
-He's not gonna do it.  -Be quiet.
我是让他还活着的唯一原因
I'm the only thing keeping him alive.
大家冷静点
Calm down, everyone.
-Mikhail!  -Sayid
我来解决 John
I'll handle this John.
John...
别让她和他说话!
Don't let her talk to him!
停下! 干吧 Mikhail!
Just do it, Mikhail!
John!
动手吧!
Finish it!
杀了我吧!
Kill me.
抱歉让你输的很难看
Sorry I beat you so bad, dude.
那你还来和我说什么
Sorry you hustled me, you mean.
我妈妈在地下室有个乒乓桌
My mom had a table in her basement,
我在里面...
and I played a lot at the insti...
待了很长时间
This place I hung out for a while.
那感觉真好
I got kinda good.
你真行啊
Well, hooray for you.
这不是你的作风
Doesn't look like at last slam
输了就输了吧...
caused any long-term damage to your forehead...
你得了3分 总比没分强吧
and you got 3 points, which is better than zero.
你想要做什么?
Something you want?
还给你些东西
Came to give you back some of your stuff,
因为你需要这些
Cause, you know, you're the kind of guy that needs stuff.
你这是安慰我吗?
You a shrink now?
她会没事的 Kate
She'll be okay, dude, Kate
我知道你在担心她 但她和Locke和Sayid在一起
I know you're worried about her, But she's with Locke and Sayid.
她不会有事的
She's gonna be fine.
谢谢你的好意 大块头
Yeah, well, thanks for the pep talk,
是Hurley...或者Hugo
It's Hurley...or Hugo, if you want.
去找个板凳吧 Hugo
Get bent, Hugo.
准备好走了吗 Locke?
You ready to go, Locke?
我一会儿就来
I'll be there in a minute.
如果这个站点已被"敌人"入侵
Has there been an incursion on this station by the hostiles?
请输入7-7
If so, enter 7-7.
Danielle! Danielle!
告诉我
Tell me something.
你曾是达摩的一员吗?
Were you ever a member of the Dharma Initiative,
还是你一开始就在撒谎?
or was everything you said a lie?
我当然是在浪费时间
Of course I'm wasting my breath.
我不是达摩的一员 但其它的都是真的
I was never a member, but everything else I told you was true.
"大清洗"后我来到了这个站点
I moved into the station after the purge.
哪个科考团队会袭击你们呢?
The purge, in which a group of scientists attacked your people?
你相不相信随你便 但这些确实发生了
Believe what you want, but that is what happened.
你的朋友..他们死了吗?
Your friends.. did he kill them?
没有
No.
他们正在搜集那个农舍可利用的资源
They're collecting whatever may be useful from the farmhouse
现在有人可以带我们去"The others"那里了
and now we have our ticket to where the others live
我们就能找到Jack和你的女儿
where we'll find your daughter and Jack
也许还能找到回家的路
and finally, perhaps, a way home.
我不会带你们去那里的
There is nothing you could do to me that would make me lead you there.
我没有说过让你带路
I didn't say you were our ticket, did I?
这张地图显示与火焰舱连接的各个电缆
This is a map showing electrical and data cabling running from the Flame here,
这个地方叫"the barracks"
to a place called "the Barracks," here.
这是个包括有水和电的住宅区
It's comprised of houses and dormitories with water and power
那些能源足够能提供给整个社区
large enough to accommodate an entire community.
那地方一定很值得拜访
Sounds like a place well worth visiting, don't you think?
你们的警惕会降低
There will come a time when your guard is down
到时我会毫不留情的杀了你们
and when it is, I will not hesitate a moment before killing you.
-你应该知道这点  -他说到点子上了
-You should know this before  -He's making an excellent point.
我们有地图
You have a map.
为什么要让他活着?
Why keep him alive?
我和丈夫到巴黎后
After my husband and I first arrived to Paris
我总是不敢走出公寓一步
I was afraid to ever leave our apartment.
所以我透过窗户看着小巷
So I would stare out the window into the alley
我看见这只猫在寻找剩饭菜
and I would see this cat looking for scraps.
一天 一群孩子把它关在一个箱子里
One day, some children came into the alley and trapped him in a box.
我看着他们往箱子里投入爆竹
I watched them light firecrackers and drop them in the box.
我从三楼就能听到它的嚎叫
I could hear him howl from three stories above.
终于 我有理由走出我的公寓
So finally, I had a reason to leave my apartment.
我救了这只猫 把它带回了家
I rescued this cat, and I brought him home.
当我阅读时 它总在身边
He sits with me when I read.
当我睡觉时 它总是发出咕噜声
He sleeps with me, and he purrs.
但..总有那么些时候
But.. every once in a while
它会咬我 抓我
he will bite me or scratch me.
它这样做是因为它害怕了
He does this because sometimes he forgets that he is safe now.
所以我任凭它咬我
So I forgive him when he bites me
因为我知道它受过的伤害
because I know what it is like to never feel safe.
都是因为你
And that is because of you.
所以今天...我只问你一件事
So today...I ask only one thing of you.
我要你向我承认
I ask you now that you show me the respect
你对我做的一切...
of acknowledging what you did to me...
是你拷问我 折磨我...
that it was you who questioned me, that tortured me...
你记得我
and that you remember me.
我记得你
I remember you.
我记得你的脸
I remember your face.
你的脸总让我心神不宁
Your face has haunted me ever since I left Iraq.
我很抱歉
I am sorry.
抱歉我对你做的一切
I am so sorry for what I did to you.
我原谅你
I forgive you.
当我丈夫回来后 我会告诉他我犯了一个错误
When my husband returns, I will tell him I made a terrible mistake
那个人不是你...
that it was not you...
然后他会放了你
and he will release you.
为什么?
Why ?
你为什么让我走?
Why are you letting me go?
我们都能做到那些孩子对这只猫做的事...
We are all capable of doing what those children did to this cat...
但我不会
but I will not do that.
我不会这样做的
I will not be that.
我们应该杀了他 Sayid
We should kill him, Sayid.
他已经说了他会杀了我们的
He already told us that he would kill us.
不
No
他是我的囚犯
He's my prisoner.
我来决定他的命运
I will decide his fate.
我可以看出这里的东西都没用了
I can see you didn't find anything worth taking.
我又玩了那个愚蠢的象棋游戏
Actually, I just played that silly chess game again
现在我知道你为什么不让我赢它了
and now I realize why you didn't want me to beat it.
那意味着什么?
Meaning what ?
你做了什么 John?
What have you done, John?
那是唯一有希望和外界联系的地方!
That place was our one hope of communication with the outside world!
那电脑说如果我们被"敌人"入侵
The computer said if there was an incursion by the hostiles
我应该输入7-7 所以我就这么做了
I should enter 7-7, so I entered 7-7.
我们应该走了
We should go.
如果周围有人的话 他们会被这里的爆炸吸引过来的
If anyone's around, this explosion is going to attract their attention.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■